[suspenseful music fades in]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[waves crashing]
[sinister beat]
[suspenseful music continues]
[wind blowing]
[waves crashing]
Papa: Okay. Mind your fingers.
[clinking]
Just like before, now.
[waves crashing]
[seagulls crying]
[glass clinks]
[higher tempo music fades in]
[suspenseful music]
[wind whistling]
- [sighs]
- [waves lapping]
[sinister music]
[waves crashing]
[dog panting]
[wave crashes]
[glass clinks]
[cork pops]
[liquid pouring]
[bottle clinks]
[sighs]
[dog whines]
What you looking at?
[clattering]
What are we gonna do today?
Make yourself useful,
and give it some thought.
[clank]
[radio playing weather forecast]
[spoon clinks]
[suspenseful music]
Checkmate.
[sea roaring]
[creaking]
[sighs]
[snores lightly]
[coughs]
Okay.
[sinister music resumes]
[exhales]
[groans]
[sea roaring]
Leave the crate
and come straight back.
The weather looks like
it's picking up.
- [boat crunching on sand]
- [wind whooshing]
[knocking on door]
[dog whines]
[sighs]
[wind howling]
[waves crashing]
[bottles clinking]
Don't come up here again.
[slam]
[waves crashing]
Most people just say thank you.
[inhales] It's very important
that you listen.
Don't ever
come up here again.
You know,
me and my uncle come up here
week after week,
bringing you supplies,
and yet you never even come down
to greet us.
Why is that?
[wind picking up]
[bottles clinking, box thumps]
[door slams]
[latch clanks]
[scoffs]
[shouts] I'm not afraid of you!
[suspenseful music]
[waves crashing]
[boat horn blows]
[wind howling]
[bottles clinking]
[waves churning, crashing]
Man On Radio:
Message to all vessels.
Gale force winds are in
serious effect across the coast.
[breathing hard]
Jessie, come on!
- [waves crashing]
- [boat horn blares]
New storm formed now heading
towards the Hebrides.
[muffled radio message
continues]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
Don't give me that look.
[waves crashing]
[shouts] Jessie!
[groaning with effort]
[shouts] Come on!
[suspenseful music continues]
- [waves crashing]
- Papa!
[strains]
[shouts] Come on!
[man talking on radio]
[sea raging, crashing]
Urgh!
[screams]
[gurgling]
[shouts] Jessie!
Uh... argh!
[wind whistling]
[kettle whistling]
[dog whining]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[kettle whistles louder]
- [high-tempo music]
- [grunts]
[waves crashing]
[straining]
[boat rumbling]
[boat motor starts, roars]
[gasps]
- [gurgling]
- [dramatic music]
[splashing]
[waves crashing]
[high-tempo music continues]
[gurgling]
[distorted gurgling]
[eerie music]
[high-tempo music resumes]
[distorted gurgling]
[eerie music]
- [splashing]
- [gasping]
[suspenseful music]
[thunder cracks]
[groaning with effort]
[grunting]
[dramatic music crescendo]
[dramatic music fades out]
[bed creaking]
Where's my uncle?
Where's my uncle?!
[wind rattling windows]
He's dead.
[gasps]
The trawler went down.
He was trapped.
[sniffs]
[melancholic music]
[sobbing]
[waves crashing]
[dog panting]
Jessie: Agh!
[inhales, grunts]
Agh!
We need to get
the swelling down.
[water dripping]
[gasps]
Why haven't you called anyone
about what happened?
Not even the police?
Who else knows we're here?
No one?
Just rest.
Mason: [sighs]
[sinister music]
- [cork pops]
- [drink pours]
[scoffs]
You have to take me back.
You can't just keep me here.
I... I mean, I... I don't even
understand why you're here.
My uncle told me
that this lighthouse
hasn't been working in years.
Yet you never leave here. Why?
My family will be
looking for me.
You don't have a family.
Your mother died
a few years back.
Never knew your father.
Your uncle's taken care of you
ever since.
Because there was no one else.
How do you know that?
Well, someone
will come looking.
[sighs]
Will they?
There's nothing here for anyone.
[sinister music continues]
[door closes]
[winces]
[drawer opens]
[music tempo increases]
[dog barking]
[door closes]
[sinister music]
[sniffs]
[dark music]
[whimpering]
[dog panting]
[whimpering continues]
[gasps]
[quietly] It's just a dream.
[exhales]
I know you're scared.
And in a lot of pain.
When you use a weapon,
you never operate from fear.
Always balance your emotions.
Keep your wits.
Hold it like this.
Your thumb up against the hilt.
Tight in the palm.
Hold it up.
Good.
That's a strong grip.
I'm gonna look at your ankle.
[dramatic music]
[waves lapping]
[snaps] Come on.
- [sobs]
- [clattering]
[high-tempo music fades in]
[bowls, cutlery clatter]
[Jessie chattering]
[radio chatter in background]
How did you know my uncle?
We served together.
In the Royal Marines.
He never told me your name.
What is it?
Would it make a difference
if you knew it?
Well, I'd at least know
what to call you.
We're doing okay so far.
Well, at least tell me
your dog's name, then.
He doesn't have one.
What?
That's crazy.
Your dog doesn't even
have a name?
Well...
I'm going to call him...
Jack.
Right, Jack? Come. Hey.
[chuckles]
[Jack panting]
Jack.
He likes the name Jack.
Black Queen... to F2.
Check.
[chuckles]
You didn't tell me you could
play chess.
You never asked.
Looks like I've got myself
a worthy opponent.
Jessie: [chuckles]
[radio continues in background]
[dramatic music]
It's infected.
- Can't we just go to a hospital?
- No.
No.
I'll get what's needed.
[sea gushing]
[suspenseful music fades in]
[dramatic music fades in]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[boat rumbling]
[suspenseful music fades in]
[traffic humming]
[tense music]
[woman speaking indistinctly]
[indistinct chatter]
Woman: Ten years ago,
the Prime Minister
assured this committee
and the nation
that her government, I quote...
"Was not and would not ever
collect data
on British citizens."
And yet, thanks to the recent
hack into MI6's servers,
we have now learned that not
only has MI6
been systematically harvesting
the personal information,
calls, emails,
and voting patterns
of the British population,
but has been doing so in order
to create an intelligence...
super-system.
An advanced surveillance network
called Total Human
Engagement Analytics,
or more affectionately, THEA.
Some of the details are,
of course, classified.
The essence of THEA is to make
better-informed decisions,
to anticipate threats
more effectively.
Woman: What you've been doing
is unlawfully invading the life
of every person
in this country.
Manafort: If they're innocent,
they have nothing to hide.
Since THEA went online,
MI6 have intercepted threats
at a rate never before imagined.
Perhaps you could simply say
thank you.
Let me be clear
on how this ends.
With you and Prime Minister
Fordham under investigation,
and THEA dismantled.
Haneron was grandstanding,
Prime Minister.
We both know the whole
thing's a circus,
just without
the entertainment value.
Haneron is gaining traction
in this election.
And this leak...
it's a national embarrassment.
We're gonna have to steady
the ship.
[sighs]
You need a sacrificial lamb.
Let's face it, Stephen.
You're probably
the best spymaster
this country has ever produced.
But you are
a hopeless bureaucrat.
We all have our shortcomings,
Prime Minister.
- [button clicks]
- PM: The tape's stopped.
It's just the two of us now.
[dramatic music]
I think this could be
a blessing.
Really?
To get you back into the shadows
where you belong.
Could be our little secret.
Indeed, ma'am.
Roberta Frost, your number two,
she'll take over as head of MI6
as an interim appointment,
and then after the election,
I'll appoint somebody
more appropriate.
Roberta's a good choice.
She's a good team player.
And we don't want any outsiders.
Exactly.
Enjoy your retirement.
Thank you, Prime Minister.
[suspenseful music]
How old is she?
About there.
...like I said we were supposed
to go in the first place,
but I thought we were gonna
go bowling instead.
That's a bit more fun, no?
We always go...
[suspenseful music continues]
...like I said we were supposed
to go in the first place,
but I thought we were gonna
go bowling instead.
That's a bit more fun, no?
[dark music]
[keyboard clacking]
[beeping]
Woman: High priority THEA alert.
We have a retinal match.
Timur Tchermoev.
He's a high-value target,
wanted for the bombing
of our embassy in Algeria.
His file is filled
with similar atrocities.
Location?
Stornoway. Outer Hebrides,
Scotland.
Repositioning satellites now.
Who's our nearest assault team?
Alpha.
Send them.
Mason: Okay.
Let the medicine do its work.
That should be as good as new.
Thank you for the sweets,
by the way.
I got these.
I hope they're okay.
It's the best I could do.
[poignant music]
I like them.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[sea churning softly]
[music playing faintly
in background]
Mason: Mm.
Smells good.
So much better than porridge.
That, young lady,
is a matter of opinion.
[Jack panting, whimpering]
[waves crashing distantly]
What?
- [cutlery clanking]
- [chair clatters]
[sinister music]
[chair scrapes]
[boat engine roaring]
What's happening?
Get in the bathroom.
Lock the door.
Don't make a sound.
Don't come out until
I come for you.
Do it, Jessie.
[Jack whimpering]
Stay.
[door closes, locks]
[clattering]
[high-tempo music]
[metal clatters]
Commando 1: Weapons free.
Kill target on sight.
[panting over radio]
[whipping, rumbling]
[steel ropes whipping, crashing]
- Agh...
- [ropes whipping]
- Argh...
- [splashing]
Find this fucker.
[high-tempo music intensifies]
[switch, lights clanking]
- [high-tempo music continues]
- [gunfire erupts]
[whimpers]
Spread out. Box him in.
[high-tempo music continues]
- [glass shattering]
- [grunting]
- [flare gun fires]
- [screaming]
[clattering]
[grunting]
[thumping]
[body thuds]
[high-tempo music intensifies]
[Jack growls]
[panting]
[barking]
- [Jack snarling]
- [man groaning]
- [Jessie sniffling]
[gunfire]
[breathing heavily]
[banging]
[door smashes]
Drop it! Jesus Christ!
[struggling]
I've found the girl.
Extracting her now.
Jack!
[music intensity fades]
- [smashing]
- Argh!
[grunting]
[sinister music]
- [struggling]
- [blows landing]
Aaargh! Argh!
[knife blade swishes]
- [gunshot]
- [thump, crash]
[smash, wood splintering]
[Jessie struggling]
[sinister music]
Let me go!
- [gunshot]
- Argh!
[gunshot]
[coughing, gasping]
[gasping]
Jessie: Who is that? Who?
Who... who are these guys?
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
Who... yeah, who are...?
I need you to wait here.
Nothing's gonna happen.
I'm coming right back.
But... but where are you going?
[gasping, crying]
[small waves breaking]
[melancholic music]
[gun clanks on floor]
[sighs]
Sorry, old boy.
[drawer opens]
I'm off the reservation.
With baggage.
Okay, I'll be there.
- [suspenseful music]
- [waves lapping]
- [gasps]
- It's time to leave.
[coughs] But w-what about Jack?
Mason: Come on.
Wha... what? What?
Jack? No, no!
Jack?
[high-tempo music]
Come on, we need to leave.
[boat motor revving]
[suspenseful music]
Aziz: Alpha team, come in.
They're all gone.
Deakins: Who the hell
is this guy?
Whoever he is,
he's not Tchermoev.
Who's our nearest
tier-one asset?
[keyboard clacking]
Workman.
[exhales] Activate him.
And notify all QRF teams
in the region to be on standby.
Find out who that girl is.
[dark music]
[phone beeps]
[Velcro rips]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music]
[high-tempo music]
[wake splashing]
Come on!
- You're hurt!
- I'll be fine.
But... but you're bleeding.
Come on.
[breathing heavily]
- [dogs barking distantly]
- Stay behind me.
I need to check something.
Wait here.
[sheep bleating]
I need to go inside.
Get the keys.
You mean steal them?
Hey, I need you to wait here.
Ever use a gun?
I shot squirrels
with my uncle's air rifle.
Good enough. Hold this.
One hand there, and one there.
Hold it tight against your body.
Keep the barrel pointed
to the dirt.
Keep your finger
off the trigger.
It's sensitive.
Get your back against the fence.
[Velcro rips]
[sniffs]
[keys jangling]
[sheep bleating]
- [door opens]
- [suspenseful music]
[whispers] Hey, hey.
That's as far as you go.
[sinister music]
Put it down.
Please.
[whispers] Whoa!
Let's... let's go slow, hey?
He's hurt. Can you help him?
[sinister music intensifies]
[door beeps, opens]
What am I looking at?
Timur Tchermoev.
His profile's been altered.
See here?
The code's been manipulated
to hide someone else.
So, when a camera captures
the real person...
Mm-hmm.
...it misidentifies him
as Tchermoev.
It's very sophisticated stuff.
Whoever did this
used self-deleting code.
[keyboard tapping]
That's our guy.
Roberta: Michael Mason.
He's one of ours?
Yeah.
But there aren't many details.
He... he was orphaned.
Former SBS operator.
K.I.A. ten years ago.
Apparently not.
Why would someone want to frame
one of our own to be targeted?
- I don't know.
- [keyboard clacking]
Whoa.
I... I just tried to access
his mission logs from Poole,
- and I got this.
- [dark music]
[beep]
Roberta: [sighs]
Okay, keep digging.
Boy: There's a man
and a girl in our house.
Oh, the ops room just
intercepted a 999 call
from a farm in Scotland,
matching Mason and our girl.
Call the ops room.
Let them know I'm on my way.
- We're all good, sir.
- Thank you, Ross.
[sinister music]
[keyboard clacking]
Shit.
[sinister music]
Boy: They have guns.
Please help.
They're holding my father.
Our target is not
who we thought.
His name is Michael Mason.
I want him caught
and brought in for questioning.
- Where's my asset?
- Workman's en route.
Boy: Please, please help.
Workman.
Good.
[keyboard clacking]
[exhales]
[phone beeps]
[keyboard clacking]
[high-tempo music intensifies]
[beeps]
[keyboard clacking]
Fuck you, Mason.
I'm... I'm not sure how good
this will hold.
I've only stitched goats
and sheep.
I'm sure it's good.
- [chair scrapes]
- Thanks.
- We'll get out of your hair.
- Man: Okay.
I'm gonna need your truck.
Man: Keys are by the front door.
Go grab them, start it up.
[quietly] I don't want you
to hurt them.
I'm not gonna hurt them. Okay?
Where's your son?
Callum!
Did you just go do something?
[sheep bleats distantly]
Callum?
I called the police.
[suspenseful music]
- [dogs barking]
- [police siren wailing]
Let's move.
Come.
Sit there. Don't move.
[police sirens wailing]
Deakins:
Local authorities are responding
to a home invasion at the farm.
Well, tell them not to engage.
Deakins: Hold a perimeter.
Do not engage.
I repeat do not engage!
We have personnel en route.
[shouting]
- Police!
- Are they going to arrest you?
It's not the police
I'm worried about.
[quietly] This way. Go, go, go.
Hey, hey, wait.
Don't open the door!
- I live here...
- [gunshot]
[gunfire]
[high-tempo music]
- [gun firing]
- [glass shatters]
Roberta: Find out
where those shots came from!
I'm sorry.
You need to stay here.
Come on.
[sinister music]
Man: He's inside!
Police!
Put the weapon down!
[grunting]
- Drop the weapon!
- [grunting]
[gasps]
- Agh! Argh!
- Ugh! Urgh...
Come on.
Officer: Huh, uh!
[police shouting]
- Hey, police. Stop!
- [spraying]
- Aargh!
- Drop the weapon!
[taser fires]
One to echo.
We have multiple men down.
[car revving]
[keys jangle]
Woman On Radio:
They're rolling out.
Hold your ground...
Get in the back.
Keep your head down.
Policeman: Get on Mason!
Patch me through to Workman!
[high-tempo music]
Deakins:
He's turned off his comms.
What the fuck is going on?
Stay down and hold on.
- [engine starts]
- [officers shouting]
[cars smash]
[gasping]
[shouting in background]
[engine revving loudly]
[glass shattering]
Officer On Radio: Bravo
two-one, we need backup immediately!
[whimpers]
[car revving]
- [cars smash]
- [Jessie screams]
[gasps]
[cars revving full speed]
- [gun fires]
- [Jessie screaming]
- [cars collide]
- [grunts]
[whimpers]
[yelps]
[tires squealing]
Ah! Uh...
[gasps, whimpering]
[screams] Agh!
[cars crashing]
[Workman grunts]
- [gunfire]
- [Jessie screaming]
[window shatters]
Ugh!
[smashing, crashing]
[police car engine revs]
- [dramatic music]
- [both groaning]
[tires spinning]
[engine revving]
[breathing heavily]
[fence smashing]
[suspenseful music]
[clattering, banging]
[brakes squeal]
We're switching cars.
Let's go.
[hissing]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic crescendo]
- [birds twittering]
- [music fades]
- Woman In Car: Excuse me.
- [police siren wailing]
Are you okay?
[suspenseful music]
- Sir, stand still...
- [gunfire]
[woman gasps in panic]
[cries out]
- [sighs]
- [sinister music]
[tapping buttons]
[line ringing]
Manafort: Hello, Roberta.
You calling to rub salt
in the wound?
Roberta: Hardly, sir.
For what it's worth,
I think the Prime Minister
sacking you was
a grave misstep.
Flattery will get you
everywhere.
How can I help you?
Does the name Michael Mason
ring any bells?
Where did you hear that name?
He took down a full
assault team...
alone.
What I'm about to say
doesn't exist
outside of this conversation.
Years ago,
we ran an off-book program
of elite operatives
called Black Kites.
Operatives untethered
from MI6's oversight.
And Mason was one of them.
Yeah. He was one of the first.
He was a prodigy.
He became our gold standard.
Then what happened?
He was sent to eliminate
a foreign intelligence officer.
Instead, he spared the target,
falsified his report,
and then disappeared.
Why would he defy orders?
We think he was turned.
I'm sure for a king's ransom.
You need to understand
something.
[suspenseful music]
Mason isn't just an assassin.
He's a precision instrument.
There's no stopping him.
You need to throw everything
you've got at him, Roberta.
Michael Mason unfortunately
has become a cancer
on all that we stand for.
Yes, sir.
[sinister music continues]
[sighs]
Ready to put your trade craft
to the test?
Am I gonna get fired for this?
Not unless I do.
I found the Black Kite files
on a backup server.
Mason was helping
an Iranian scientist defect
after he gave us everything
on their nuclear program.
Instead of protecting him,
Mason was ordered to kill him
for deniability.
It looks like he refused.
[suspenseful music]
Good girl, Maddie.
[sinister music fades in]
Damn it, Roberta.
Some people just can't
help themselves.
[car humming gently]
You okay?
You think I can't handle
the truth
about who you really are,
but I can.
Well... do you have family
somewhere?
No.
You never wanted one?
A wife, kids?
[sighs] It complicates things.
I'd rather it be complicated,
then.
And have my mum back.
My uncle too.
Now I have no one.
[poignant music]
I wish I could tell you
life would always be fair.
But you already know the truth
to that.
No kid should have to go through
what you did.
Just don't ever let it break
your spirit.
No matter what.
Okay?
[paper crumpling, unfolding]
Here.
At least you had Jack.
He was your family.
Better you keep it.
[church bell ringing]
Okay, there's a camera up
on the wall in front of us.
There's also one behind us.
I want you to get out
on my side,
keep your head down
and keep it forward.
[suspenseful music]
[system beeping]
[sighs]
[keyboard tapping]
[phone beeping]
[birds singing]
[sinister music]
So, when did you find religion?
Today...
when a ghost called me.
Oh, we have different
interpretations
of what "baggage" means.
Just saying.
[car engine roaring]
[light music playing on radio]
[birds singing]
[keys jangling]
Uh, no, that's the workshop.
Um...
I'm always building
one thing or another.
Just be careful, though,
there's lots of tools about.
Uh, Jessie?
Why don't you go get a drink?
The kitchen's in the back.
If you want me to leave
so you guys can talk,
you can just say that.
[footsteps receding]
Hey, hey...
It's okay.
Spirited girl.
Who is she?
What are you doing here?
Her uncle and I,
we served together.
I need a way out... for her.
Then I'll start figuring out
how they found me.
Don't tell me you've got
sentimental in your old age?
- [suspenseful music]
- She's just a kid
who was in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Christ, Mason...
[pills rattle]
[keyboard clacking]
Meet THEA.
I helped build it
before I left the circus.
The big question is...
how the hell did they find you
after I buried you?
[sinister music]
Shit.
When it was time for you
to disappear, I...
I changed your identity
to an oil worker in Aberdeen.
A nobody.
But someone figured it out,
and swapped it to this guy.
A high-value terrorist
on the watch list.
Which you know carries
an interagency kill order.
Manafort.
You... you really think
he still wants you dead
after all this time?
I broke the only rule
that matters to him.
Fuck his rules.
You refused to kill
an innocent man,
that you promised to help
after he helped us.
Can you shut it down?
Not from here.
I mean, it wouldn't matter
anyway. You've been ID'd.
All those years on that island.
You should have stayed dead,
Mason.
Yeah, that's my problem.
I just need you to keep
Jessie safe.
Manafort knows who she is now...
which makes her a loose end.
You care about her, don't you?
This is where we part ways.
Can you keep her here?
Look, Mason, I... I can't.
Why?
He has cancer.
My mum took the same meds
before she...
[poignant music]
I'm sorry I'm such a drag
to you.
Hey, Jessie, wait.
[dark music]
Is she right?
Doctors say I might get
one more Christmas.
Oh, Jesus.
I'd help you if I could.
But you know I can't be
responsible for her.
My hands are tied.
What if I go to Kamal?
He has the means
to get her out...
- undetected.
- Kamal Shah?
- [sinister music]
- No. No, no, no way.
- Not an option!
- Hey, look.
He's the best at what he does.
Yeah, because
he's a violent trafficker.
And you haven't got MI6
behind you to control him now.
Let me worry about that.
Just help me get to him.
Can you do that?
Listen, I... I can tell you
when to turn left or right.
That's about it.
Good enough.
[birds twittering]
Hey, Jessie. It's time to go.
Hey, Jessie, come on.
Were you really gonna
leave me here?
I'm sorry.
Your safety is the most
important thing to me.
Please.
Fine.
[clattering]
- [quietly] Go stand by the wall.
- But...
Just do it!
[whispers] Stand by the wall.
[ominous music]
[fire poker clinks]
[door creaks]
[ominous music intensifies]
[clock ticking]
[suspenseful music fades in]
[rapid gunfire]
[yelps]
Jesus!
- [gunfire continues]
- Hurgh!
- [crashing]
- Aaargh!
- Urgh!
- Argh!
- [blow lands]
- Ooh!
- [grunting]
- [smashing]
[grunting]
[ominous music]
Argh!
[grunting continues]
[crashing]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[blade clicks]
- [suspenseful music]
- [grunting resumes]
[shattering]
[suspenseful music continues]
[grunting]
[gunshot]
[ominous music]
Let him go.
[tearful] Just let him go.
- Argh!
- [thud]
- [grappling]
- [Jessie screams]
[nail gun shots]
Come on!
[gunfire]
[smashing]
Get here in now, go!
Go, go, get in!
- [car doors slam]
- [engine revs]
[grunts, smashes]
[high-tempo music]
[gunfire]
Jesus!
Who was that?
Him.
20 years ago.
[panting]
[phone beeps]
[suspenseful music]
Ross?
We're doubling down,
get your team ready.
Yes, sir.
Booth: The Wi-Fi in there
will suffice for my needs.
Here, take my hat and coat.
Help you hide those good looks.
Right.
Use only for an emergency,
or you know they'll trace you
in a heartbeat.
Yeah, we're gonna
have to switch motors.
They know we're in this one now.
[poignant music]
You take care, young lady.
Thank you.
[dramatic music]
I wish you'd killed that man.
I know it's wrong to say that,
but...
Maybe I'm becoming like you.
You're nothing like me, Jessie.
And I'm keeping it that way.
But how do you know?
[chuckles]
Because I've seen
who you really are.
Look... by tonight, all of this
will be behind you.
You'll start a brand-new life...
somewhere normal,
somewhere safe.
And alone.
[dark music]
What will you do?
You can't go back
to your island.
There's always another island.
I could come with you.
You don't want this life.
Always on the run,
looking over your shoulder...
And you do?
Hey, Jessie,
you need to understand.
The only way that I can
protect you...
is to stop the people
that are doing this.
[exhales]
[suspenseful music]
[sirens wailing]
[people shouting]
[suspenseful music continues]
You need to stay close to me,
all right?
[suspenseful music resumes]
[train clattering distantly]
[siren wailing
in background]
Any sign of Mason?
No. We have nothing.
[sighs] He knows what
he's doing.
You're right.
I found an unknown login to
THEA from outside MI6.
Roberta: I have
a bad feeling.
Can you ID?
No.
There is...
there is something I can try.
Whatever it is,
do it quickly.
[taps keyboard,
computer bleeps]
- [keyboard clacking]
- [high-tempo music]
[train clattering]
[distant chatter]
[sinister music]
There's a camera.
It'll see us.
Let's hope it's working.
Sorry, mate. Invite only.
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
- [grunting]
- [blows continue]
Aargh!
Take me to Kamal,
or I'll break your
other wrist.
[high-tempo music]
[bleeping]
[tapping furiously
on keyboard]
[sighs]
Well played, Roberta.
My trap worked. I got him.
It's...
Oh, shit.
- That's...
- Stephen Manafort.
[sinister music]
I know.
We'll deal with him later.
Get me every camera
in this club, now!
[club music thumping]
Let's keep this walk
nice and smooth.
[music volume increases]
Tell him it's Michael Mason.
Do you know Michael
Mason, boss?
Michael Mason.
Look at you.
No country, no badge.
Just a poor bastard who
thought he had friends in the game.
Who's she?
I need a way out...
of the country for
her. Tonight.
New identity.
Somewhere off grid.
No.
No?
How do you think you've been
allowed to operate
for all these years, Kamal?
With impunity.
And with the luxury of
getting rid of your competition
at the same time.
By ratting them out to
Manafort and I.
Manafort's gone.
Not gone...
unshackled.
He's more dangerous than
ever to us both.
- You're lying.
- Am I?
The second the security
camera outside saw me walk in here,
into your club, every
operative MI6 has within 25 miles
was activated to
bring me in.
I reckon
you've got ten minutes, tops.
All I need is for you
to get her out.
And I'll go cut the head
off the snake.
Bury all our dirty little
secrets with him.
Wait here.
[club music continues]
[music thumping distantly]
[door closes]
[sinister music fades in]
Please come with me.
You heard the deal
I made with him.
I need to honor my side.
Honor your side?
I think you wanna die.
What's that supposed
to mean?
You don't think you have
anything to live for.
If you really wanted to,
you'd come!
Hey, people like me don't
get to go and live a normal life!
You keep telling
yourself that.
[whispers] Hey, hey...
- You're stronger than this.
- No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
I need you to be.
Just promise me you're not
going to die?
Exactly.
Roberta: Right,
where's my tactical team?
- En route.
- I want Mason and the girl
taken in alive.
They are not to open fire.
- [sinister music]
- Car's out front.
How far out is your team?
They're still en route, sir.
Where the fuck are you?
[van roaring]
Thirty seconds out, sir.
The girl
is his Achilles' heel.
Use that to your advantage.
Copy that, sir.
[guns loading]
[door opens]
Passport, ID and
20,000 euros.
She goes to our safe house
in Spain for now.
Boat leaves Isle of Dogs
in 30 minutes. It won't wait.
Just make sure you finish
what you started.
If you handle your end,
I'll handle mine.
[zipping]
[tires squealing]
Wait on the other side
of the square.
Let's move. All
right, let's go.
[people chattering happily]
This is Zulu, two
minutes out.
Do we have
an exact location inside?
Aziz: Wait,
you're not already there?
That's a negative.
[high-tempo music continues]
Manafort. Tell them that
there's a rogue team already inside.
They need to get in
there now! Now!
[club music thumping]
[man cries out in pain]
- [grunting]
- Argh!
[clubbers cheering]
[club music continues]
[people screaming]
It's okay.
- [silenced gunshots]
- Argh!
[woman screams]
[chaotic shouting]
[club music thumping]
[people chattering]
- [screams]
- [gunfire]
[shouting and gunfire
continues]
[screaming]
- [grunting]
- [gunshots]
[club music thumping]
[struggling]
Argh!
[Jessie grunting]
- [gunshot]
- [woman screams]
- [people screaming]
[gunfire continues]
[glass smashing]
Get out of here!
Move out of the way!
[screaming]
Mason!
- [loud bang]
- [alarm blares]
Arthur. Manafort's guards
have got Jessie.
Move, move, move.
Out of the way! Out the way!
Found her. Hold on.
Out the front entrance.
Cut across the square
and turn south.
She's being carried
towards a black transit van.
Open it up!
- I've got her! Move, move!
- Help me!
- Go, go, go!
- [Jessie screaming]
Get ready!
He's gonna be coming
for her!
Get in there!
[struggling]
Where are you going?
Get in there!
[Jessie panting]
[clubbers screaming]
I don't see Mason.
There!
[clubbers screaming]
[dramatic music]
Mason's heading
right towards you.
[car screeches]
[commandos shouting]
[people whimpering]
- [gunshot]
- [screaming]
Move!
[struggling]
[gunshot]
- [blows landing]
- [grunting]
[crying]
[screaming]
Move!
Fucking move.
[gunshots echo]
[panicking]
[sirens blaring]
[sinister music]
I got you.
It's okay.
I got you, Jessie.
[exhales]
I got you.
You okay?
- [suspenseful music]
- Time to go.
[engine starts]
[police siren wailing]
[dramatic music fades in]
[dramatic music continues]
There's your ride.
Hey.
You're gonna be okay.
Come on.
Gonna lower her down.
Man: You've gotta hurry!
- Ready? It's time to go.
- [upset] No.
- The boat won't wait.
- No, no, no. You...
You said you can't live
a normal life, but you're wrong.
You just have to come
on the boat with me
and we can... we
can disappear
and we can have
a normal life.
- Come on.
- Please. No, please!
- Please!
- The boat won't wait.
You're all I have now!
I don't wanna leave you.
Hey. Jessie.
- No!
- Listen to me.
[sobs]
- Jessie.
- No!
This is the only way
I can keep you safe.
I'm sorry.
No! I'm not...
I'm not leaving without you!
[poignant music]
I have to save you!
You saved me already.
- Come on.
- [gunshot]
[Jessie screams]
- Now, Jessie!
- No!
- [yelps]
- Okay, she's safe.
[boat engine roars]
No, no, please!
[sobs]
[gunshots echo]
[dramatic music]
[gunshots echo distantly]
[boat motor roaring]
Do you even know why
you're doing this?
Does it matter?
You can't save her either.
- [blows landing]
- [grunting]
[loud thud]
- [ominous music]
- [grunts]
[clanking]
[grunting, groaning]
[grunting]
[dramatic music fades in]
[both grunting]
- [grunting continues]
- Argh!
[breathing heavily]
[clanking]
[thump]
[sinister music]
[chain rattles]
Newly appointed MI6 head,
Roberta Frost,
is dealing with
the fallout...
[gentle music playing]
[drink pouring]
[sighs]
[sniffs]
You were my dearest...
my greatest weapon.
And then you broke
the rules.
Black Kites know one law
above all: loyalty.
You put your conscience
first and the mission second.
I finally put humanity
over blind obedience.
Oh, yeah. There it is.
The righteous martyr.
And a foolish one. You
allowed a civilian into this game.
A child! What good is
all that humanity
with her blood
on your hands?
That's not gonna happen.
And you know it.
I don't want that either.
You really think you can
outrun what you are?
We are who we are, Mason.
I have been given complete
autonomy
to make Black Kites
stronger than ever.
I want you with me...
by my side, as we were.
You're the very reason I
didn't pull the trigger ten years ago.
And why I have to now.
[body falls with a thud]
[sinister music]
[people chattering happily]
[soft music]
What's up? Anything new?
Just having some cocoa
and reading a book.
Zoom in and up-res.
[computer bleeping]
Er, maybe we should
start exploring
other ways to find him.
He hid from us for
ten years...
until her.
It's a matter of when.
Deakins: Wait.
It's him.
Your friend said this was
for you.
[packet rustles]
- Where is he?
- He was there a moment ago.
[dramatic music]
[music playing]
[singer vocalizing]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music ends]